{
    "id": "f10baa6901424d6587c36446a650ed51",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "To hit a person when he is down is a contemptuous thing to ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "be done",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bece0bc3eb7e4dc8ab8d9a9a2c9507bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "In 1665, a great epidemic ............................................. the death of 63,000 people in London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caused",
                "has caused",
                "had caused"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7436a08bd1c4ae296ea2295162d8ec9"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... his lack of interest in the affairs of the society, the members decided to depose him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Because of",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b1c706d6f35478f8dec07c83294f3c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ...................................... thousands of foreign stamps since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has collected",
                "is collecting",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "08d313f21748485ab7cb4bf9917e635c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We watched the airplane until it disappeared ....................................... the clouds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c8a6de4db484578b58325fc5625dec7"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to activists, action ......................................... long ago to preserve forests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must take",
                "must be taken",
                "must have been taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fda7fdba5f704ce6a2e3633e1f68e5ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "When Sophia said that she was coming to see me I wondered what .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the problem was",
                "was the problem"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3eabdacc397f4808a997e327dc91f295"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested that I .......................................... walk on and try to get help while he stayed with the injured person.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6cfb9b89baf468dae4ef042fb28bd7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack told his sister that he .......................................... her help in solving the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40a2a7610ee14007bbc1c8f596760b04"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge paid no attention ......................................... the boy was unhappy at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "to the fact that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0dc08c5f8bfc489da156b31ed3ad15c2"
        }
    ]
}